Register of the Ronald Reagan Radio Commentary Sound Recordings, 1967-1980
Hoover Institution Archives
Ronald Reagan radio commentary sound recordings
1967-1980
2000C19
Hoover Institution Archives
3 manuscript boxes, 2 oversize boxes, 1 card file box, 2 cubic foot boxes (7.5 linear feet)
This collection contains sound recordings, transcripts, correspondence, and other documents related to the radio broadcast series Viewpoint with Ronald Reagan and Ronald Reagan Radio Commentary as well as the LP records Ronald Reagan: The Great Moments (aborted) and Ronald Reagan: On the Air. O'Connor Creative Services produced both the radio series and the LPs. A variety of domestic and international topics are covered including the economy, oil, guns, religion, taxes, energy, and welfare. Era-specific subjects such as conflict in Southeast Asia (Vietnam, Cambodia) and the Torrijos-Carter Treaties that returned control of the Panama Canal to Panama receive considerable attention.
Access
Box 3 and 5-7 are closed. Use copies of all sound recordings in this collection are available for immediate access.
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos or films during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all audiovisual material is immediately accessible.
Acquisition Information
Acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives in 2000.
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog Socrates at http://library.stanford.edu/webcat. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in Socrates is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Related Materials
Ronald Reagan subject collection, Hoover Institution Archives
Citizens for Reagan records, Hoover Institution Archives
Deaver & Hannaford, Inc. records, Hoover Institution Archives
Peter D. Hannaford papers, Hoover Institution Archives
Annelise G. Anderson papers, Hoover Institution Archives
Historical Note
The series Viewpoint with Ronald Reagan and Ronald Reagan Radio Commentary were produced by O'Connor Creative Services and concern political conditions in the United States and abroad. The titles Viewpoint with Ronald Reagan and Ronald Reagan Radio Commentary were used at different times to describe the series: Viewpoint for the programs produced in 1975 and 1976 and Ronald Reagan Radio Commentary for the programs produced in 1977 and 1978. Programming was halted during the times Reagan was a declared candidate for the presidency: the first occurrence being November 1975, resuming September 1, 1976 after he lost the nomination; the second being November 1979, when he declared for the 1980 presidential election. Programming ceased altogether following the 1980 election.
Reagan recorded his radio commentaries in batches of fifteen programs (five a week). During the period of January 8, 1975, to December 12, 1978, these recordings were pressed on vinyl LPs. Each LP contained three weeks of programming. At least once during this period Reagan recorded twenty programs at a studio session instead of fifteen, leaving fifteen to be distributed while he was on a foreign trip. Commentaries were committed to magnetic tape following the December 12, 1978, program.
In 1977, O'Connor Creative Services began planning Ronald Reagan: The Great Moments, the first attempt to issue select commentaries commercially. Tracks were sequenced and artwork selected, however the project was aborted in 1978. Later in 1978, a comparable LP, Ronald Reagan On the Air: A Collection of His Most Memorable Broadcasts (O'Connor Creative Services, 1978), was successfully created and issued. In 2001, a five-CD collection titled Reagan in his Own Voice (Simon & Schuster Audio, 2001) was issued and includes many more commentaries as well as recorded thoughts by Nancy Reagan, Harry O'Connor, Peter Hannaford, Martin Anderson, Annelise Anderson, Edwin Meese III, and others. A selection of twenty recordings was also included on CD in Reagan's Path to Victory (The Free Press, 2004), eight of which overlapped with the Simon & Schulster Audio). Transcripts of these recordings were published in the books Reagan in His Own Hand (The Free Press, 2001) and Reagan's Path to Victory (The Free Press, 2004).
Scope and Content of Collection
This collection contains sound recordings, transcripts, correspondence, and other documents related to the radio broadcast series Viewpoint with Ronald Reagan and Ronald Reagan Radio Commentary as well as the LP record albums Ronald Reagan: The Great Moments (aborted) and Ronald Reagan: On the Air. O'Connor Creative Services produced both the radio series and the LPs. A variety of domestic and international topics are covered, including the economy, oil, guns, religion, taxes, energy, and welfare. Era-specific subjects such as conflict in Southeast Asia (Vietnam, Cambodia) and the Torrijos-Carter Treaties that returned control of the Panama Canal to Panama receive considerable attention.
Audio recordings of these commentaries are included on the records or tapes in this collection. For preservation purposes, the original recordings have been reformatted and are available as digital use copies in the Hoover Archives reading room.
Selected recordings from this series were issued commercially on the compilation LP Ronald Reagan On the Air: A Collection of His Most Memorable Broadcasts (O'Connor Creative Services, 1978) and the CD collection Reagan in His Own Voice (Simon & Schuster, 2001).
Transcripts of the recordings issued on Reagan in His Own Voice were published in the book Reagan in His Own Hand (Simon & Schuster, 2001), and are included in Box 2 of this collection.
Arrangement
The collection is organized into 2 series: Subject File and Sound Recordings. The sound recordings are further divided into subseries according to media format: LP records, cassettes, open reel tapes, and compact discs.
O'Connor Creative Services.; Reagan, Ronald.; Conservatism.; Phonorecords.; Phonotapes.; Radio broadcasting--United States.; United States--Politics and government--1974-1977.; United States--Politics and government--1977-1981.; United States--Politics and government.
- Subject File, 1974-1980. (Box 1-2)
  Scope and Contents note
  Drafts, proofs, transcripts of recorded programs, memos and correspondence related to the Ronald Reagan Radio Commentary and Viewpoint radio programs and the LP record album, Ronald Reagan: The Great Moments
  - Contracts, proofs, transcripts, memos, and correspondence related to the Ronald Reagan Radio Commentary and Viewpoint with Ronald Reagan radio programs and the LP record album, Ronald Reagan: The Great Moments, 1977 (Folder 1: 1)
  - Photographs and postcards of Ronald Reagan, his associates, and proposed artwork for the LP record album Ronald Reagan: The Great Moments, (24 photographs, 13 negatives, 7 contact sheets, 12 postcards), dates unknown (Folder 1: 2)
  - Correspondence, affiliate rosters, and clippings related to the radio programs Viewpoint and Ronald Reagan Radio Commentary, 1974-1980 (Folder 1: 3)
  - Transcripts of Viewpoint with Ronald Reagan programs 1 through 11, 1977 (Folder 1: 4)
    See Program List for a full list of program titles and dates
  - Viewpoint with Ronald Reagan transcripts of programs 12 through 22, 1977 (Folder 2: 1)
  - Viewpoint with Ronald Reagan transcripts of programs 76-2A, 76-9A and Ronald Reagan Radio Commentary transcripts of programs 77-20 through 77-23, 1976-1977 (Folder 2: 2)
  - Ronald Reagan Radio Commentary transcripts of programs 78-1 through 78-8, 1978 (Folder 2: 3)
  - Ronald Reagan Radio Commentary transcripts of programs 78-9 through 78-15, 1978 (Folder 2: 4)
  - Ronald Reagan Radio Commentary transcripts of programs 79-1 through 79-7, 1979 (Folder 2: 5)
  - Ronald Reagan Radio Commentary transcripts of programs 79-8 through 79-15, 1979 (Folder 2: 6)
- Sound recordings, 1974-1980. (Box 3)
  - Sound recordings of Viewpoint with Ronald Reagan and Ronald Reagan Radio Commentary programs (LP records), 1975-1978. (Box 3)
    See Program List for a full list of program titles and dates. Items closed; use CD access copies in box 9. Programs include: 75-01 through 75-05, 75-07 through 75-13, 75-16, 75-19 through 75-20, 75-24, 76-01 through 76-19, 77-20 through 77-24, 78-01 through 78-17
  - Sound recordings of public appearances by Ronald Reagan (compact sound cassettes), 1967-1977 (Box 4)
    Box 5 of this collection includes copies of some of these cassettes on open reel tape. The cassettes, however, appear to be the masters. Arranged in creator-designated numerical order
    - Numbered (12 items) (Box 4)
      - 1. Ford-Reagan meeting afternoon, 18 August 1976; ABC Today, 19 August 1976; GOP Convention 19 August 1976, Reagan address after acceptance speech, undated (Box 4)
      - 1B. Ronald Reagan's speech to the Republican National Convention, Kansas City, Missouri, 19 August 1976 (Box 4)
      - 2. Ashboro, North Carolina, 19 March 1976 (Box 4)
      - 3. Ronald Reagan's "Thank You" tape, including GOP convention "Thursday Night" speech (Box 4)
      - 4. Farewell to staff, press availability, interview, 19 August 1976 (Box 4)
      - 5. Press availability and Reagan remarks at Marlborough Girls Prep School, Los Angeles, 6 June 1974; Gubernatorial inauguration, 1971 (Box 4)
      - 6. Sound recording of (1) a production about the end of the administration of Governor Reagan, and (2) "The Wit and Humor of Ronald Reagan,", July 1974 undated (Box 4)
        Part one is about the end of the Governor Reagan administration, dated July 1974. This program sounds like it is an audio recording of a television program. Part two is a JRH production features clips of Ronald Reagan relating jokes and other funny stories from his career. Part two is duplicated on unnumbered item two below, "The Wit and Humor of Ronald Reagan."
      - 7. Gubernatorial inauguration, 1971; Speech side 1; Press availability, Reagan remarks at Marlborough Girls Prep School, 6 June 1974 (Box 4)
      - 8. Manchester, New Hampshire, 28 January 1976; Asheville, North Carolina, 27 January 1976 (Box 4)
        Handwritten date on label of side B is incorrect. The Asheville, North Carolina speech occurred in 1976
      - 9. Governor Reagan inauguration, 2 January 1967 (Box 4)
      - 10. Governor Reagan inauguration, 5 January 1967 (Box 4)
      - 11. Sound recording of the 1976 Republican Convention (Box 4)
        This is a transfer from videotape
    - Unnumbered (2 items) (Box 4)
      - Reagan missing "We the People" segment, undated (Box 4)
      - The Wit and Humor of Ronald Reagan, undated (Box 4)
        This JRH production features clips of Ronald Reagan relating jokes and other funny stories from his career.
  - Sound recordings of public appearances by Ronald Reagan and the Viewpoint with Ronald Reagan and Ronald Reagan Radio Commentary programs (7-inch open reel tapes), 1975-1979. (Box 5)
    See Program List for a full list of program titles and dates. Some of these reels appear to be copies of cassettes in box 4. Several tapes are undated
    - From Reagan cassette #4, side 1 and 2, edited (Box 5)
    - From Reagan cassette #5, side 1, edited (Box 5)
    - From Reagan cassette #6, side 2, edited (Box 5)
    - From Reagan cassette #8, side 1, edited (Box 5)
    - From Reagan cassette #8, side 2, edited (Box 5)
    - From Reagan cassette #10, side 1, edited (Box 5)
    - From Reagan cassette #10, side 2, edited (Box 5)
    - From Reagan cassette #11, sides 1 and 2 (Box 5)
    - Reagan speech plug for Abilene, Texas, and autobiography (Box 5)
    - Reagan LP elements #11 (Box 5)
    - Reagan 1-76 A (Box 5)
    - Reagan 1-76 B (Box 5)
    - Ronald Reagan 'On the Air,' master cassette dubber (Box 5)
    - VP-RR (Disc) (Box 5)
  - Sound recordings of Viewpoint with Ronald Reagan and Ronald Reagan Radio Commentary programs (10-inch opn reel tapes), 1976-1979. (Box On shelf)
    See Program List for complete program titles and dates. Arranged by program number. Some of these reels are copies of discs in box 3; others are unique. Closed. Use copies available
    - No. 23 (Folder On shelf)
    - No. 24 (Folder On shelf)
    - No. 76-10 (Folder On shelf)
    - No. 77-20 (Folder On shelf)
    - No. 78-1 (Folder On shelf)
    - No. 78-2 (Folder On shelf)
    - No. 78-3 (Folder On shelf)
    - No. 78-4 (Folder On shelf)
    - No. 78-5 (Folder On shelf)
    - No. 78-7 (Folder On shelf)
    - No. 78-8 (Folder On shelf)
    - No. 78-9 (Folder On shelf)
    - No. 78-10 (Folder On shelf)
    - No. 78-11 (Folder On shelf)
    - No. 78-13 (Folder On shelf)
    - No. 78-14 (Folder On shelf)
    - No. 78-15 (Folder On shelf)
    - No. 78-16 (Folder On shelf)
    - No. 78-17 (Folder On shelf)
    - No. 79-1 (Folder On shelf)
    - No. 79-2 (Folder On shelf)
    - No. 79-3 (Folder On shelf)
    - No. 79-4 (Folder On shelf)
    - No. 79-5 (Folder On shelf)
    - No. 79-6 (Folder On shelf)
    - No. 79-7 (Folder On shelf)
    - No. 79-8 (Folder On shelf)
    - No. 79-9 (Folder On shelf)
    - No. 79-10 (Folder On shelf)
    - No. 79-11 (Folder On shelf)
    - No. 79-12 (Folder On shelf)
    - No. 79-13 (Folder On shelf)
    - No. 79-14 (Folder On shelf)
    - No. 79-15 (Folder On shelf)
    - [no number] (Folder On shelf)
  - Sound recordings of the Viewpoint with Ronald Reagan and Ronald Reagan Radio Commentary programs (compact discs), 1975-1979. (Box 6)
    Includes programs digitized from phonodiscs and reels in boxes 3-6 as well as programs missing from those boxes.
- Program list of Viewpoint and Ronald Reagan Radio Commentary, 1975-1979
  - Food Stamps, Program 75-01, 8 January 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Consumer Protection, Program 75-01, 8 January 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Inflation, Program 75-01, 8 January 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Boondoggle, Program 75-01, 8 January 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Cuba, Program 75-01, 8 January 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Unemployment (1), Program 75-01, 8 January 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Unemployment (2), Program 75-01, 8 January 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Unemployment (3), Program 75-01, 8 January 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Bureaucrats, Program 75-01, 8 January 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Civil Service, Program 75-01, 8 January 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - 3 R's, Program 75-01, 8 January 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Postal Service, Program 75-01, 8 January 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Fair Trade, Program 75-01, 8 January 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Inflation Fighting, Program 75-02, 1 February 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Supply and Demand, Program 75-02, 1 February 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Surprise Tax Bills, Program 75-02, 1 February 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Energy Problems, Program 75-02, 1 February 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Rocky's Story, Program 75-02, 1 February 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Public Employees, Program 75-02, 1 February 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Viet Nam [Vietnam] Policy, Program 75-02, 1 February 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Capitalism-Socialism, Program 75-02, 1 February 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Volunteerism, Program 75-02, 1 February 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Incredible Bread Machine, Program 75-02, 1 February 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Red China, Program 75-02, 1 February 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Federal Budget, Program 75-03, 14 February 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Détente, Program 75-03, 14 February 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Peru Revolution, Program 75-03, 14 February 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Mozart vs Sibelius, Program 75-03, 14 February 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
    Guest: Peter Hannaford
  - The Delta Queen, Program 75-03, 14 February 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - A Cuba Documentary, Program 75-03, 14 February 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Farm Facts, Program 75-03, 14 February 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Tax Plan #1, Program 75-03, 14 February 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Tax Plan #2, Program 75-03, 14 February 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Tax Plan #3, Program 75-03, 14 February 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Arms Limitations, Program 75-03, 14 February 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Crisis of Democracy, Program 75-03, 14 February 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Unemployment #1, Program 75-04, 27 February 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Unemployment #2, Program 75-04, 27 February 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - W. Germany / Inflation, Program 75-04, 27 February 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - National Debt #1, Program 75-04, 27 February 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - National Debt #2, Program 75-04, 27 February 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Congress and Security, Program 75-04, 27 February 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - The Work Ethic, Program 75-04, 27 February 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Land Planning, Program 75-04, 27 February 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Price of Beef, Program 75-04, 27 February 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Private Government, Program 75-04, 27 February 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - N.H. [New Hampshire] Senate Contest, Program 75-04, 27 February 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Recession vs Inflation, Program 75-04, 27 February 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Southeast Asia, Program 75-05, 12 March 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Energy Sources, Program 75-05, 12 March 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Capital Punishment, Program 75-05, 12 March 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Vacation Exchange Program, Program 75-05, 12 March 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - The Superintendent's Dilemma, Program 75-05, 12 March 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Oil Talk, Program 75-05, 12 March 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Tiffany and Company, Program 75-05, 12 March 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Cold Beer, Program 75-05, 12 March 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Regulations, Program 75-05, 12 March 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Federal Retirement Pensions, Program 75-05, 12 March 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Easy Voting, Program 75-05, 12 March 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - The Money Supply, Program 75-05, 12 March 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Portugal #1, Program 75-06, 1 March 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Portugal #2, Program 75-06, 1 March 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Energy #1, Program 75-06, 1 March 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Energy #2, Program 75-06, 1 March 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Campaign Law, Program 75-06, 1 March 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Indochina #1, Program 75-07, 3 April 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Indochina #2, Program 75-07, 3 April 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Satellites, Program 75-07, 3 April 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Utility Subsidies, Program 75-07, 3 April 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Postal Feedback, Program 75-07, 3 April 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Patent Proposals, Program 75-07, 3 April 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - The New Congress, Program 75-07, 3 April 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Abortion Laws, Program 75-07, 3 April 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Welfare Program #1, Program 75-07, 3 April 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Welfare Program #2, Program 75-07, 3 April 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Welfare Program #3, Program 75-07, 3 April 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - London #1, Program 75-08, 1 April 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - London #2, Program 75-08, 1 April 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - London #3, Program 75-08, 1 April 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Regulations / New Wave #1, Program 75-08, 1 April 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Regulations / New Wave #2, Program 75-08, 1 April 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Farm Workers Union, Program 75-08, 1 April 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - No Time to Confuse, Program 75-08, 1 April 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Vietnam, Program 75-08, 1 April 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Land Use, Program 75-08, 1 April 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Peace, Program 75-08, 1 April 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Government: Big vs Small #1, Program 75-08, 1 April 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Government: Big vs Small #2, Program 75-08, 1 April 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - The Amazing DeBolts, Program 75-09, 1 May 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - The Washington Media, Program 75-09, 1 May 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Italian Bureaucracy and the U.S. Treasury, Program 75-09, 1 May 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - United Nations, Program 75-09, 1 May 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Red Sea, Program 75-09, 1 May 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Nuclear Power, Program 75-09, 1 May 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Recession's Cause, Program 75-09, 1 May 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Portugal, Program 75-09, 1 May 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Government Computers, Program 75-09, 1 May 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Adoption, Program 75-09, 1 May 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Agency for Consumer Advocacy, Program 75-09, 1 May 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - George Meany and Economics, Program 75-10, 1 May 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Communism, The Disease, Program 75-10, 1 May 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Soviet Superiority, Program 75-10, 1 May 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - The EPA Strikes Again, Program 75-10, 1 May 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Panama Canal, Program 75-10, 1 May 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Boondoggles'' Foe, Program 75-10, 1 May 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Radical Chic Revisited, Program 75-10, 1 May 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Falling Dominoes, Program 75-10, 1 May 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Truth in Spending, Program 75-10, 1 May 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Congress vs Local Government, Program 75-10, 1 May 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Tax Loopholes, Program 75-10, 1 May 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Is This the Land of Our Fathers?, Program 75-11, 1 June 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
    Guest: Maureen Reagan
  - Is Government Our Big Brother?, Program 75-11, 1 June 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Seen Your Doctor Lately?, Program 75-11, 1 June 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Big Mo, Program 75-11, 1 June 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Inflation As Tax, Program 75-11, 1 June 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Cost Overruns, Program 75-11, 1 June 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Gun Control #1, Program 75-11, 1 June 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Gun Control #2, Program 75-11, 1 June 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Gun Control #3, Program 75-11, 1 June 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Button Button, Program 75-11, 1 June 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Letters to the Editor, Program 75-11, 1 June 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Business, Profits, Myths and Realities, Program 75-11, 1 June 1975 (Box 8, Box 1)
  - Free Enterprise, Program 75-12, 1 June 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Law and Order, Program 75-12, 1 June 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Job Hunting, Program 75-12, 1 June 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Budget "Uncontrollables," Program 75-12, 1 June 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Aquaculture, Program 75-12, 1 June 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Stopping Vandalism, Program 75-12, 1 June 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Mariana Islands, Program 75-12, 1 June 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Congressional "Perks", Program 75-12, 1 June 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Samizadt, Program 75-12, 1 June 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - M.I.A., Program 75-12, 1 June 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Pacific Legal Foundation, Program 75-12, 1 June 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Polls on Government, Program 75-12, 1 June 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Chile, Program 75-13, 8 July 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - UNICEF, Program 75-13, 8 July 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Socialized Medicine I, Program 75-13, 8 July 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Socialized Medicine II, Program 75-13, 8 July 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Community Work Experience Program, Program 75-13, 8 July 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Phu Quoc, Program 75-13, 8 July 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Welfare Reform Corporations I, Program 75-13, 8 July 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Welfare Reform Corporations II, Program 75-13, 8 July 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Welfare Reform Corporations III, Program 75-13, 8 July 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Do Away with IRS?, Program 75-13, 8 July 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Turtles and Aquaculture, Program 75-13, 8 July 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Somalia, Program 75-13, 8 July 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Equal Rights Amendment: Pro, Program 75-14, 1 August 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Equal Rights Amendment: Con, Program 75-14, 1 August 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Soviet Life, Program 75-14, 1 August 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - World Affairs Report, Program 75-14, 1 August 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - "Why Don't They ____?" Program 75-14, 1 August 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)